Hisham Khatib Collection - Mediterranean Pilgrimage Association Resource AD_MC_030_ref150
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
- Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000057; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000057j; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000057k; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; Palestine; Jerusalem; English Writing; Dome of the Rock; Buildings; Architecture; Religious Sites; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Photographic Prints
  - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000057l; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000057m; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; Photographic Prints; English Writing; Dome of the Rock; Palestine; Jerusalem; Religious Sites; Column/Colonnade; Architecture
  - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000057n; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; Al-Aqsa Mosque; Palestine; Jerusalem; English Writing
  - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000057o; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; English Writing; Al-Aqsa Mosque; Mosques; Religious Sites; Buildings; Architecture; Palestine; Jerusalem; Islamic Architecture
  - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000057p; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; English Writing; Al-Aqsa Mosque; Palestine; Jerusalem
  - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000057q; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; English Writing; Photographic Prints; Al-Aqsa Mosque; Mosques; Religious Sites; Architecture; Column/Colonnade; Buildings; Interiors; Islamic Architecture
  - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000057r; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; English Writing; Palestine; Jerusalem; Al-Aqsa Mosque
  - Booklet entitled "A Brief Guide to Al-Haram Al-Sharif Jerusalem"., 1927; 150_000057s; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
- Postcards of Bethany, Jericho and the Tomb of Lazarus., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000058; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Albumen Prints; Jericho; Al-Eizariya/Bethany; Buildings; Streets/Roads; English Writing; French Writing; Spanish Writing; Italian Writing; Group Portraits; Outdoors; Traditional Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Men; Women; Children; Tombs; Religious Sites; Palestine; West Bank
- Postcards of Rachel's Tomb and Solomon's Pools., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000059; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; French Writing; English Writing; Spanish Writing; Italian Writing; Bethlehem; Tombs; Solomon's Pools/El-Burak; Religious Sites; Palestine; Buildings; Architecture; Hills; West Bank; Bilal bin Rabah Mosque/Rachel's Tomb
- Three postcards of the Church of the Nativity., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000060; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; French Writing; English Writing; Spanish Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; Column/Colonnade; Churches; Church of the Nativity; Religious Sites; Architecture; Buildings; Interiors; Religious Imagery; Bethlehem; West Bank; Palestine
- Two postcards of Bethlehem., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000061; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Bethlehem; Palestine; West Bank; Christmas; Crowds; Parades/Processions; Buildings; Agriculture; Religious Holiday; Religious Ceremony
- Postcards of Bethlehem and the Dead Sea., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000062; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Photographic Prints; Bethlehem; West Bank; Palestine; Buildings; Men; Weapons; Guns; Animals; Lakes; Dead Sea; English Writing; French Writing; Italian Writing; Spanish Writing; Traditional Dress
- Two postcards of Nazareth., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000063; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Nazareth; Galilee; Palestine; Buildings; Religious Sites; Synagogues; Architecture; English Writing; Hills
- Two postcards of Nazareth., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000064; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Albumen Prints; Landscapes; Mountains; English Writing; Nazareth; Galilee; Palestine; Religious Imagery; Group Portraits
- Two postcards of Mary's Well (Virgin's Fountain)., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000065; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Photographic Prints; Albumen Prints; English Writing; Nazareth; Galilee; Palestine; Group Portraits; Outdoors; Women; Children; Girls; Boys; Mary's Well/Ain il-Adhra; Buildings; Architecture; Men; Animals; Camels; Traditional Dress; French Writing; Italian Writing; Spanish Writing
- Two postcards of Nazareth., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000066; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Nazareth; Galilee; Palestine; English Writing; French Writing; Italian Writing; Spanish Writing; Buildings; Mount Tabor/Jabal at-Tur; Landscapes; Mountains
- Two postcards of Nazareth., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000067; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Architecture; Nazareth; Galilee; Palestine; Hotels; English Writing
- Postcards of Tiberias and Hebron., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000068; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Sea of Galilee/Lake Tiberias; Lakes; Buildings; Tiberias/Tabariyyah; Palestine; Mountains; Hebron/Al-Khalil; West Bank; Men; Animals; Traditional Dress
- Postcards of Haifa and Tiberias., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000069; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Photographic Prints; English Writing; French Writing; Italian Writing; Spanish Writing; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Sea of Galilee/Lake Tiberias; Lakes; Tiberias/Tabariyyah; Palestine; Haifa; Seas; Mediterranean Sea; Buildings; Mount Carmel /Al-Karmil; Mountains
- Postcards of Mount Tabor and Jaffa., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000070; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Mount Tabor/Jabal at-Tur; Landscapes; Mountains; Galilee; Palestine; Jaffa; French Writing; English Writing; Italian Writing; Spanish Writing; Mediterranean Sea; Seas; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Buildings
- Two postcards of Haifa and Mt. Carmel., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000071; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Photographic Prints; Palm Trees; Mount Carmel /Al-Karmil; Haifa; Palestine; Landscapes; Men; Hats; Buildings; Mediterranean Sea; Seas; Mountains; Religious Sites; French Writing; English Writing; Italian Writing; Spanish Writing
- A postcard titled "Flowers from the Holy Land"., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000072; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; English Writing
- Postcards of Cana of Galilee and Jacob's Well., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000073; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; English Writing; Individual Portraits; Men; Traditional Dress; Outdoors; Buildings; Galilee; Palestine; Greek Writing; French Writing; Chandeliers; Religious Clothing; Religious Imagery; Interiors; West Bank; Nablus; Religious Sites; Albumen Prints
- (Blank page), Circa 1900-1928; 150_000074; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
- (Blank page)., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000075; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
- Tourist agency tickets from Larnaca, Cyprus., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000076; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  English Writing; Cyprus; Larnaca, Cyprus
- Map of Sea of Galilee and the Dead Sea from Thomas Cook & Son., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000077; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Maps; English Writing; Galilee; Palestine; Dead Sea
- Reuters news bulletin to Cyprus., 8 May 1928; 150_000078; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  English Writing
- Reuters news bulletin to Cyprus., 10 May 1928; 150_000079; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
- Three postcards of Smyrne (Izmir)., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000080; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Izmir, Turkey; Turkey; Smyrna; Religious Sites; Mosques; Buildings; Architecture; Aegean Sea; Seas; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Carriages/Coaches; Men; Streets/Roads; French Writing
- Two postcards of Smyrne (Izmir) Port., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000081; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; French Writing; Turkey; Izmir, Turkey; Ports; Smyrna; Aegean Sea; Seas; Buildings; Architecture; Men; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Carriages/Coaches
- Two postcards of Smyrne (Izmir)., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000082; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Smyrna; Izmir, Turkey; Turkey; Aegean Sea; Seas; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Buildings; Tombs; French Writing
- (Blank page)., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000083; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
- (Blank page)., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000084; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
- (Blank page)., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000085; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
- Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul)., 1928; 150_000086; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul)., 1928; 150_000086a; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    English Writing; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Turkey; Arabic Calligraphy; Books
  - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul)., 1928; 150_000086b; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; English Writing; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Turkey
  - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul)., 1928; 150_000086c; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; English Writing; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Turkey; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Bosphorus; Seas; Boats/Ships; Buildings
  - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul)., 1928; 150_000086d; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; English Writing; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Turkey; Bosphorus; Men; Buildings; Forts/Castles; Roumeli Hissar Castle
  - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul)., 1928; 150_000086e; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; English Writing; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Turkey; Photographic Prints; Hippodrome of Constantinople; Hagia Sophia; Religious Sites; Architecture; Column/Colonnade; Arabic Calligraphy; Buildings; Monuments; Interiors
  - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul)., 1928; 150_000086f; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; Istanbul, Turkey; Turkey; Constantinople; English Writing; Blue Mosque/Sultan Ahmed Mosque; Architecture; Religious Sites; Mosques; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Column/Colonnade; Reservoirs; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Islamic Architecture
  - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul)., 1928; 150_000086g; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    English Writing; Turkey; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Religious Sites; Mosques; Suleymaniye Mosque; Interiors; Arabic Calligraphy; Tombs; Coffins/Caskets; Sculpture; Museums; Islamic Architecture
  - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul)., 1928; 150_000086h; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Turkey; Photographic Prints; Prinkipo/Büyükada (Turkey); Landscapes; Prince Islands, Istanbul, Turkey; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Bosphorus; Suleymaniye Mosque; Mosques; Religious Sites; English Writing; Buildings; Architecture; Islamic Architecture
  - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul)., 1928; 150_000086i; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; English Writing; Turkey; Istanbul, Turkey; Constantinople; The Golden Horn; Boats/Ships; Flags; Transportation; Bosphorus; Hills
  - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul)., 1928; 150_000086j; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; Istanbul, Turkey; Turkey; Constantinople; English Writing; Group Portraits; Turban; Men; Outdoors; Traditional Dress; Buildings; Architecture
  - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul)., 1928; 150_000086k; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; English Writing; Turkey; Istanbul, Turkey; Constantinople; Photographic Prints; Seas; Buildings; Dolmabahce Palace; Architecture; Palace
  - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul)., 1928; 150_000086l; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; English Writing; Constantinople; Galata Bridge; Galata, Istanbul, Turkey; Istanbul, Turkey; Turkey; New Mosque / Yeni Cami; Mosques; Religious Sites; Architecture; Buildings; Crowds; Street Lamps; Beyazit Square, Istanbul, Turkey; Beyazit Tower; Photographic Prints; Public transportation; Islamic Architecture
  - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul)., 1928; 150_000086m; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
    Books; English Writing; Istanbul, Turkey; Turkey; Constantinople; Grand Bazaar; Shops; Men; Photographic Prints; Markets
  - Tourism information booklet on Constantinople (Istanbul)., 1928; 150_000086n; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
- A postcard of Brasserie Universelle Restaurant, Paris., Circa 1928; 150_000087; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Postcards; Albumen Prints; Photographic Prints; Paris, France; France; French Writing; Cars; Transportation; Men; Women; Hats; Restaurants; Buildings; Architecture; Streets/Roads; Street Lamps
- (Blank page)., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000088; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
- (Blank page)., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000089; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
- Newspaper clipping with an image of an entrance to the Shwedagon Pagoda., Circa 1928; 150_000090; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Newspapers/Magazines; Architecture; Buildings; English Writing; Religious Sites; Temples; Men; Traditional Dress; Statues; Shwedagon Pagoda; Myanmar; Yangon, Myanmar
- Inside Back Cover- Newspaper clipping about the Shwedagon Pagoda., Circa 1928; 150_000091; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)
  Newspaper Clippings; Newspapers/Magazines; English Writing; Shwedagon Pagoda; Myanmar; Yangon, Myanmar; Temples; Religious Sites
- Back Cover., Circa 1900-1928; 150_000092; 1 Photographic Prints (Object Digital copy only: 030_ref150)